(this.webpackJsonpnovasoft_assignment=this.webpackJsonpnovasoft_assignment||[]).push([[0],{11:function(e,t,n){},2:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20hero%20in%20the%2080s%20animated%20video%20game%20%27Dragon%27s%20Lair%27%3F","correct_answer":"Dirk%20the%20Daring","incorrect_answers":["Arthur","Sir%20Toby%20Belch","Guy%20of%20Gisbourne"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What%20is%20the%20scientific%20name%20for%20modern%20day%20humans%3F","correct_answer":"Homo%20Sapiens","incorrect_answers":["Homo%20Ergaster","Homo%20Erectus","Homo%20Neanderthalensis"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Books","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20is%20Ron%20Weasley%27s%20middle%20name%3F","correct_answer":"Bilius","incorrect_answers":["Arthur","John","Dominic"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who%20is%20the%20creator%20of%20the%20comic%20series%20%22The%20Walking%20Dead%22%3F","correct_answer":"Robert%20Kirkman","incorrect_answers":["Stan%20Lee","Malcolm%20Wheeler-Nicholson","Robert%20Crumb"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Board%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"At%20the%20start%20of%20a%20standard%20game%20of%20the%20Monopoly%2C%20if%20you%20throw%20a%20double%20six%2C%20which%20square%20would%20you%20land%20on%3F","correct_answer":"Electric%20Company","incorrect_answers":["Water%20Works","Chance","Community%20Chest"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Jamaica%3F","correct_answer":"Kingston","incorrect_answers":["Rio%20de%20Janeiro","Dar%20es%20Salaam","Kano"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"When%20did%20Jamaica%20recieve%20its%20independence%20from%20England%3F%20","correct_answer":"1962","incorrect_answers":["1492","1963","1987"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Kangaroos%20keep%20food%20in%20their%20pouches%20next%20to%20their%20children.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%202013%20how%20much%20money%20was%20lost%20by%20Nigerian%20scams%3F","correct_answer":"%2412.7%20Billion","incorrect_answers":["%2495%20Million","%24956%20Million","%242.7%20Billion"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"How%20old%20was%20Lyndon%20B.%20Johnson%20when%20he%20assumed%20the%20role%20of%20President%20of%20the%20United%20States%3F","correct_answer":"55","incorrect_answers":["50","60","54"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In%20World%20of%20Warcraft%20lore%2C%20who%20organized%20the%20creation%20of%20the%20Paladins%3F","correct_answer":"Alonsus%20Faol","incorrect_answers":["Uther%20the%20Lightbringer","Alexandros%20Mograine","Sargeras%2C%20The%20Daemon%20Lord"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%20the%20game%20%22Subnautica%22%2C%20a%20%22Cave%20Crawler%22%20will%20attack%20you.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20device%20that%20allows%20for%20infinite%20energy%20in%20the%20anime%20%22Dimension%20W%22%3F","correct_answer":"Coils","incorrect_answers":["Wires","Collectors","Tesla"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20Cream%20the%20Rabbit%27s%20mom%20in%20the%20%22Sonic%20the%20Hedgehog%22%20series%3F","correct_answer":"Vanilla","incorrect_answers":["Peach","Strawberry","Mint"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"These%20two%20countries%20held%20a%20commonwealth%20from%20the%2016th%20to%2018th%20century.","correct_answer":"Poland%20and%20Lithuania","incorrect_answers":["Hutu%20and%20Rwanda","North%20Korea%20and%20South%20Korea","Bangladesh%20and%20Bhutan"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Television","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"Which%20of%20these%20voices%20wasn%27t%20a%20choice%20for%20the%20House%20AI%20in%20%22The%20Simpsons%20Treehouse%20of%20Horror%22%20short%2C%20House%20of%20Whacks%3F","correct_answer":"George%20Clooney","incorrect_answers":["Matthew%20Perry","Dennis%20Miller","Pierce%20Brosnan"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Music","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"From%20which%20album%20is%20the%20Gorillaz%20song%2C%20%22On%20Melancholy%20Hill%22%20featured%20in%3F","correct_answer":"Plastic%20Beach","incorrect_answers":["Demon%20Days","Humanz","The%20Fall"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Scotland%20voted%20to%20become%20an%20independent%20country%20during%20the%20referendum%20from%20September%202014.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%20Left%204%20Dead%2C%20which%20campaign%20has%20the%20protagonists%20going%20through%20a%20subway%20in%20order%20to%20reach%20a%20hospital%20for%20evacuation%3F","correct_answer":"No%20Mercy","incorrect_answers":["Subway%20Sprint","Hospital%20Havoc","Blood%20Harvest"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20was%20the%20last%20colony%20the%20UK%20ceded%20marking%20the%20end%20of%20the%20British%20Empire%3F","correct_answer":"Hong%20Kong","incorrect_answers":["India","Australia","Ireland"]}]')},25:function(e,t,n){},31:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var r=n(3),i=n.n(r),o=n(9),s=n.n(o),a=(n(11),n.p,n(25),n(1));var c=function(e){e&&e instanceof Function&&n.e(3).then(n.bind(null,35)).then((function(t){var n=t.getCLS,r=t.getFID,i=t.getFCP,o=t.getLCP,s=t.getTTFB;n(e),r(e),i(e),o(e),s(e)}))},u=(n(12),n(10)),l=n.n(u),h=(n(15),n(2)),d=n(16),m=n(17),y=n(19),f=n(18),g=n(32),w=n(33),p=n(34),b=function(e){Object(y.a)(n,e);var t=Object(f.a)(n);function n(){var e;return Object(d.a)(this,n),(e=t.call(this)).getQuestions=function(){h().then((function(t){e.setState({questionQuiz:t})}))},e.state={questionQuiz:[],score:0,responses:0,right:"none",wrong:"none",currentQuestion:0},e}return Object(m.a)(n,[{key:"selectOption",value:function(e,t){e===t?(console.log("right"),this.setState({right:""})):(console.log("wrong"),this.setState({wrong:""}))}},{key:"nextQuestion",value:function(){var e=this.state.currentQuestion+1;this.setState({currentQuestion:e,right:"none",wrong:"none"})}},{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this,t=0;return"easy"===h[this.state.currentQuestion].rating?t=3:"hard"===h[this.state.currentQuestion].rating?t=5:"medium"===h[this.state.currentQuestion].rating&&(t=4),Object(a.jsxs)(a.Fragment,{children:[Object(a.jsx)("progress",{value:this.state.currentQuestion/20*100,max:"100",className:"quizProgressBar"}),Object(a.jsxs)("div",{className:"body",children:[Object(a.jsxs)("h2",{children:["Question Number ",this.state.currentQuestion+1," of 20"]}),Object(a.jsx)("h6",{children:"Entertaiment Board Exam"}),Object(a.jsx)("h4",{children:h[this.state.currentQuestion].question}),Object(a.jsx)(l.a,{total:"5",rating:t}),Object(a.jsx)(g.a,{children:Object(a.jsxs)(w.a,{xs:"2",children:[Object(a.jsx)(p.a,{className:"button1",children:Object(a.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){return e.selectOption(h[e.state.currentQuestion].correct_answer,h[e.state.currentQuestion].correct_answer)},children:h[this.state.currentQuestion].correct_answer})}),Object(a.jsx)(p.a,{className:"button1",children:Object(a.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){return e.selectOption(h[e.state.currentQuestion].incorrect_answers[0],h[e.state.currentQuestion].correct_answer)},children:h[this.state.currentQuestion].incorrect_answers[0]})}),Object(a.jsx)(p.a,{className:"button1",children:Object(a.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){return e.selectOption(h[e.state.currentQuestion].incorrect_answers[1],h[e.state.currentQuestion].correct_answer)},children:h[this.state.currentQuestion].incorrect_answers[1]})}),Object(a.jsx)(p.a,{className:"button1",children:Object(a.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){return e.selectOption(h[e.state.currentQuestion].incorrect_answers[2],h[e.state.currentQuestion].correct_answer)},children:h[this.state.currentQuestion].incorrect_answers[2]})})]})}),Object(a.jsx)("h1",{style:{display:this.state.right},children:"Correct"}),Object(a.jsx)("button",{style:{display:this.state.right},onClick:function(){return e.nextQuestion()},children:"Next Question"}),Object(a.jsx)("h1",{style:{display:this.state.wrong},children:"Wrong"}),Object(a.jsx)("progress",{value:"30",max:"100",className:"progressBar"})]})]})}}]),n}(i.a.Component);s.a.render(Object(a.jsx)(a.Fragment,{children:Object(a.jsx)(b,{})}),document.getElementById("root")),c()}},[[31,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.d49b551d.chunk.js.map